<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stories on TAIMA</title>
    <link>https://7timothyhn.github.io/TAIMA.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stories on TAIMA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:03:50 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://7timothyhn.github.io/TAIMA.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Story 1: Private the guard dog</title>
      <link>https://7timothyhn.github.io/TAIMA.github.io/posts/private-the-guard-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:03:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://7timothyhn.github.io/TAIMA.github.io/posts/private-the-guard-dog/</guid>
      <description>Ah, it is not easy being the best guard dog in town, but I will give you pointers on what it takes to be the best. Every day starts with training. First 10 barking pushups, ‘woof’ 1, ‘woof 2’, ‘woof’ 3… ‘woof’ 10. You might be thinking why barking pushups? That is because it warms up the lungs and readies you for anything that can happen. It also adds the benefit of making sure that any intruders become scared and filled with fright making fear the day they come here again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Story 2: Rambo the adventurer</title>
      <link>https://7timothyhn.github.io/TAIMA.github.io/posts/rambo-the-adventurer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:03:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://7timothyhn.github.io/TAIMA.github.io/posts/rambo-the-adventurer/</guid>
      <description>On today’s adventure, I will finally defeat the illusive noise machine. Humans call it cars. Yes, I am Rambo Indiana Jones the adventurer. Rediscoverer of lost new jewels, the uncoverer of hidden secrets. On today&amp;rsquo;s adventure, I find the elusive bone of KFC. As with any adventure, I leave the base through the secret tunnel under the swinging wall, humans call it a gate. Now we sniff.
Sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Story 3: The All-Powerful Princess Lucy </title>
      <link>https://7timothyhn.github.io/TAIMA.github.io/posts/the-all-powerful-princess-lucy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:03:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://7timothyhn.github.io/TAIMA.github.io/posts/the-all-powerful-princess-lucy/</guid>
      <description>It has been years since I have conquered this domain. These servants have been doing well but I still cannot understand why they keep standing on two legs. Are they always scared? Well, that is to be expected. Oh yes, it is very hard being me every morning when I wake up with my servants still lying in bed. How could they? isn&amp;rsquo;t it that a proper servant should wake up before their master?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Story 4: The Last Dodo Bird</title>
      <link>https://7timothyhn.github.io/TAIMA.github.io/posts/the-last-dodo-bird/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:03:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://7timothyhn.github.io/TAIMA.github.io/posts/the-last-dodo-bird/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The final flock, the last set of dodos on earth. Dodo 1, dodo 2, dodo 3, and dodo 4. Will any of them make it past the ice age?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;hellip;to be continued</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
